Zack, what's up, man? Dan Morgan with
the Panthers, man. How you doing? What's
going on? I'm doing great.
>> How do you feel about being a Carolina
Panther, man?
Man, it'd be a blessing, man. Be
amazing. Let's do it, man. You're a
Panther, man.
Congrats.
Appreciate that. Appreciate that. Yeah,
you I can't wait to get down there. Are
you with your family? Yeah, I got my
family with me right now. All my
peoples. Awesome, man. Enjoy and
congrats. I'm going to pass you off to
our owner, David Tepper.
All right, bet. Appreciate it.
>> man. Congrats.
Thank you. Hi, Zack. How are you doing?
I'm doing great. How you doing?
>> Good. Good. Your whole family's there,
you said? Yeah, my whole family with me
right now. That's good. That's good.
What do you got a nickname or something?
What do they call you there?
Zack. Is that right?
Yes, sir.
>> All right. I knew you had to have
something there, so.
All [laughter] right. I'm going to give
you over to coach here, okay? All right,
bet.
>> All right, bye-bye.
Hey, let's go, man. Let's do it.
How you feeling?
>> [applause]
>> Hey, this is this is an exciting moment
for all of us, really. Um as we went
through it, man, you just you're a
Panther. The way you play, uh the style
you play with, the awareness and all
that, man. I'm so excited. So excited to
get you here. I'm going to pass you over
to Ronaldo, coach Naddy. He's going to
talk to you right now.
Yes, sir. Zack.
What's going on?
>> Congratulations, man. Appreciate it.
Enjoy your enjoy your family and
friends, and we'll get to work soon, all
right? I will. I'll see you soon. All
right. Talk to you soon. Yes, sir.
Congrats, [applause] man.
>> [music]